apeasternpower.com 2013-08-06

# ::APEPDCL::

| 

**Privacy Policy**

We at EPDCL respect the privacy of everyone who visits this website and are committed to maintain the privacy and security of the personal information of all visitors to this website but does not promise or guarantee the same. Our policy on the collection and use of personal information and other information is outlined below.

**  
Personal Information :**

We do not require personal information to obtain access to most of our website. We collect personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include name, title, company, address, phone number, email address, and other relevant data. Questions or comments submitted by visitors may also include in personal information. We collect and use personal information for business purposes in order   

* To provide tender downloads, information, grievance, etc and take advantage of certain other features of our website.

* To provide information or interactive services through this website, to your e-mail address 

* To seek your feedback or to contact you in relation to those services offered on our website.

* To process and respond to requests, improve our operations, and communicate with visitors about our services.

* To allow you to access certain contents of our website.

We will not use or share, either within EPDCL or with a third party, any information collected at this page for direct marketing purposes. 

To the extent required or permitted by law, we may also collect, use and disclose personal information in connection with security related or law enforcement investigations or in the course of cooperating with authorities or complying with legal requirements.

**  
Non personal information :**

At this web site, information sent by your web browser, may be automatically collected. This information typically includes your domain name . It may also contain your user name . Other examples of information may be collected by our server include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect the visitor's computer to the Internet, operating system and platform, the average time spent on our website, pages viewed, information searched for, access times, websites visited before and a visitor visits our website, and other relevant statistics. 

We use the information we automatically receive from your web browser to see which pages you visit within our website, which website you visited before coming to ours, and where you go after you leave. We at EPDCL develop statistics that are helpful to understand how our visitors can use this website. We use this information in the aggregate to measure the use of our website and to administer and improve our website. 

**  
Information placed on your computer**

We may store some information such as cookies on your computer when you look at our website. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to the hard drive of a visitor's computer for record-keeping purposes. This information facilitates your use of our website and ensures that you do not need to re-enter your details every time you visit it. You can erase or choose to block this information from your computer if you want to. Erasing or blocking such information may limit the range of features available to the visitor on our website. 

**  
Security**

We have implemented technology and policies, with the objective of protecting your privacy from unauthorized access and improper use but does not promise or guarantee the same. SPDCL does not make any warranty that the contents of the Site are free from infection by viruses or anything else which has contaminating or destructive properties.

**  
Service Providers**

We give your information to the people and companies that help us provide the services we offer. For example, we may use outside vendors to help host our website, serve photos and videos, process payments, or provide search results. In some cases we provide the service jointly with another, such as the APonline. In all of these cases our partners must agree to only use your information consistent with the agreement we enter into with them, as well as this privacy policy.

**  
Third Parties**

For your convenience, this page may contain certain hyperlinks to other DISCOMS pages as well as to websites outside EPDCL such as APGENCO,APTRANSCO etc. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites, even if you access those using links from our website. We can make no promises or guarantees regarding data collection on the hyper-linked pages and on websites that are not owned by EPDCL. We recommend that you check the policy of each website you visit, or link from, and contact the owners or operators of such websites if you have any concerns or questions.

**  
Contacting Us**

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details you have supplied us with, please contact us. If you wish to change or delete any of the personal information you have entered whilst visiting our website or if you have any questions about our privacy statement. Privacy policy is subject to change at the discretion of EPDCL.
